A.D.
M.
Due to its declining birthrate of the human popula- tion,
Akibat dari turunnya tingkat kelahiran populasi manusia,
this country has turned into a nation of cats.
negara ini menjadi negeri para kucing.
Cat Country Japan.
Negara Kucing Jepang.
Door-to-Door Salescat
Kucing Sales Keliling
I have many, many fine wares today.
Kami punya banyak, banyak sekali barang yang bagus loh!
It's a door-to-door salescat.
Ada kucing sales.
He came to our house too, huh?
Ke rumah kita juga ternyata.
Indeed. What an absolute nuisance of a cat.
Iya nih. Dasar kucing pengganggu.
But apparently, the goods arrive inside this box.
Tapi sepertinya, barangnya diantar pakai kardus ini.
Yume, go buy something.
Yume, belanja sana.
Eh? What's with that?
Lah? Kok gitu?
This box, you see… is super comfy to get inside.
Asal tahu saja, kardus ini… enak banget buat rebahan di dalam.
This boy really understands us.
Dia benar-benar paham kami.
Mhm-hmm.
Mhm-hmm.
It won't be a waste to make a purchase.
Tidak ada ruginya belanja.
Plenty of fine wares, plenty indeed. Please, go ahead.
Barang bagusnya ada banyak, banyak sekali. Silakan dipilih.
You're a smooth talker.
Pintar sekali dagangnya.
Catalog
Katalog
Let's see…
Coba lihat…
I wanna see it too!
Ai juga mau lihat dong!
Wow, there's so much stuff I've been looking for!
Wah, banyak barang yang Ai cari selama ini!
Did you find anything you want?
Ada yang Anda inginkan?
I did!
Ada!
The rest depends on your generosity!
Sisanya tergantung kebaikan hati Yume!
The salescat is winning them over.
Kucing sales ini makin banyak temannya.
You cats are too honest with your greed, I'm scared of the bill.
Kalian terlalu jujur sama niat kalian, aku jadi ngeri mau bayar.
So please, just one item each.
Jadi tolong ya, masing-masing satu saja.
Ehh?!
Heh?!
Thank you very much. We will ship them immediately.
Terima kasih banyak. Barang akan segera kami kirim.
We bought some good stuff.
Kita dapat barang bagus nih.
I guess so.
Iya.
The next day.
Keesokan harinya.
Delivery!
Paket!
Yay! Yay! Yume!
Hore! Hore! Yume!
Yeah, yeah.
Iya, iya.
Thanks for your hard work.
Terima kasih banyak, Pak.
Hurry! Take it out of the box!
Cepat! Keluarkan dari kotaknya!
Yes, yes, I'm coming.
Iya, iya, sebentar.
Let's see…
Coba kita lihat…
Okay, here. Sorry for the wait.
Oke, ini dia. Maaf kelamaan.
Phew, so cozy.
Fyuuh, nyamannya.
TL TM TS MX-QC AI Transcribe was utilized
TL TM TS MX-QC AI Transcribe diutilisasikan
: geckyzz
: geckyzz